{
    "id": "540bb40f649f4778be7fa166023232ff",
    "title": "Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I …………………. him yesterday.",
            "description": "The present perfect cannot be used with past time expressions.",
            "answers": [
                "visited",
                "have visited",
                "had visited"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "89070e33994a447598b46aa5e546c974"
        },
        {
            "question": "We …………………. to the park last week.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "went",
                "have gone",
                "had gone"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c3ad2e62ca2f460d88a665b635d601a9"
        },
        {
            "question": "You must ……………………. the instructions.",
            "description": "To listen to is to pay attention to hear.",
            "answers": [
                "listen",
                "listen to",
                "hear"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4cf58ede850f4bfab7d3a7cc68a5d840"
        },
        {
            "question": "Always …………………. the truth.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "speak",
                "tell",
                "say",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b373139e0c3d4b789f56b31b08c2312c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her dad died two years ……………………",
            "description": "Ago is used to count from a present moment to a past moment. ",
            "answers": [
                "ago",
                "before",
                "back"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "783341f944ee49b4a54864d7798e9d4c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………. that movie last night.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "watched",
                "have watched",
                "had watched"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7d4f0802b4bc4164a938dce962f91483"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………… to the boss about my holiday.",
            "description": "When there is no time reference, the present perfect is more commonly used to talk about finished events. ",
            "answers": [
                "spoke",
                "have spoken",
                "had spoken"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b4072f42b8f741a9bc46badea59fc33c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was …………………… for murder.",
            "description": "The past tense of hang is hanged when we are talking about killing someone by hanging. ",
            "answers": [
                "hanged",
                "hung",
                "hunged"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a9b941cd7056490ca687640fa4487b59"
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………… the pictures on the wall.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hung",
                "hang",
                "hanged"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bd1b56a6493042d69de1a1598dba2c8e"
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………… under the tree.",
            "description": "When lie means to recline, its past tense is lay. ",
            "answers": [
                "lay",
                "lie",
                "lied",
                "laid"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8dd1a5509abf4e2eac30a2e2f1bde8f0"
        },
        {
            "question": "I heard them ........................... in the other room.",
            "description": "Hear is followed by an infinitive without to.",
            "answers": [
                "talk",
                "to talk"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7c6cfd788fb34d4a9e3c948570144d5d"
        },
        {
            "question": "He reached the station after the train ……………………..",
            "description": "We use the past perfect for the earlier of two past actions. ",
            "answers": [
                "left",
                "has left",
                "had left"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1f7b8b40ee78469189f6c42de9ec9a4e"
        }
    ]
}